<Characters>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A Paradise Lost</Title>
		<Character>Protector</Character>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>Once I had a family- a husband, and a daughter. We lived in a haven- a place where the spreading dark had not yet reached. It was a hidden place, protected from the evils of the world. We had crops and animals and fields of fertile earth for them to grow. The water from the streams was clean and cool, and the miles of surrounding forest hid us from prying eyes. I doubt it still remains. When I have since searched for it I have found myself wandering in circles amongst endless dunes and wasted plains.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A Paradise Lost</Title>
		<Character>Protector</Character>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>There were others in the haven- families, survivors, refugees, and wanderers like yourself. Together we worked the land, but never were we one people. We were too different, some spoke a different language, some were from a different culture. We were forced together by hardship, but never did we truly bond. Some of us were born in the sanctuary, innocent of the wider world, others looked at the world through stricken eyes, never quite seeming present.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A Paradise Lost</Title>
		<Character>Protector</Character>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>With every wanderer that passed through, every vagrant that found a home with us, the tension among us grew. We worried the haven would be discovered. There were those of us who welcomed any who needed shelter, and there were those who rejected and distrusted outsiders. As time went on our community grew, and with each new member came stories from the outer world- stories of barbarism, murder, and inhumanity. The bonds between us grew brittle, and it was not long before they reached breaking point.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A Paradise Lost</Title>
		<Character>Protector</Character>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>A bleached, wide-eyed wastelander came to our village. He was not like others that had come, there was something unhinged in him. Nevertheless, we found him a bed, fed and watered him, and left him to rest. He would not speak, but his leering eyes danced across every man, woman, and child he passed. Ill at ease we turned in for the night. In the early hours of the morning we were woken by a peal of bells. A young woman had been found, her beaten body lay across the threshold of the wastelander's hut. There was no hesitation, no discussion on what was to be done, we simply drew him from his tent, and cut his throat.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A Paradise Lost</Title>
		<Character>Protector</Character>
		<PartNumber>5</PartNumber>
		<Text>When the graves were filled we argued about what should be done. Words turned to accusations, and accusations into insults. By midday the first stone had been thrown, and sure enough others followed. The village turned to chaos, so I gathered my husband and daughter together and we ran as far into the forest as we could. There were others- families, couples, elders, and children, all running from the village. We could hear the pursuit behind us. The people we had lived with every day now hunted us like we were animals. I did not dare to look back, I only ran. By the time the shouts and screams had died away I was lost. The trees had thinned, and the rich soil turned to the sand and dirt of the great wasteland. I turned to find my family, but I could not see them. I tried to return to the village, but I could not find my way back. To this day I have not seen them. I tell myself they are lost now, but I will keep searching, I will hold out hope until the day I die.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>What Lies Within</Title>
		<Character>Beast</Character>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>My rage is eternal, enduring through the red dust and dark fire of our broken world. I have no enemies, for those that look upon my countenance see only death, but still I cut down those who stand before me- those whose eyes betray the rotting soul within. There is a dark shadow within us all, a hidden thing kept at bay by our civil self. It is in our most passionate moments that it is set free, free to do what our primal instinct knows to do. They say that the world fell because evil tainted our minds. They are wrong.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>What Lies Within</Title>
		<Character>Beast</Character>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>The devil is a part of us, it is a reflection of our surface selves, the inversion of our conscious mind. It is the essence in the air that drew it out, empowering it, and allowing it to maraud openly. But I have controlled it, I let it escape, feed, exert it's will through my hand. It is this freedom that prevents it from taking a hold of me. I acknowledge it, and so we coexist. There is no greater power in the world than the unchained beast bound to the will of its master.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>What Lies Within</Title>
		<Character>Beast</Character>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>We must exert our will to remain in control. We allow the beast to exist, and without us it would die. We must train it to know this. A covenant must be made. One that allows our darkest thoughts to be free. I revel in my freedom, I have shirked the shackles of civilisation to sate my primal thirst. Do not care for those who would do you harm. Instead liberate them, spill their blood on the sand, feed the animal within you.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>What Lies Within</Title>
		<Character>Beast</Character>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>What there is beyond death I do not know. Maybe the pearlescent gates of faith are real. Perhaps we go to the halls of our ancestors, to live forever amongst our mothers and fathers. Or perhaps there is only darkness- an obsidian infinity. One day we all shall discover what lies beyond. Until then we search only for reason and meaning. And only some of us may find it.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>What Lies Within</Title>
		<Character>Beast</Character>
		<PartNumber>5</PartNumber>
		<Text>That is why I have turned to the beast. It gives me life, a purpose- though raw and uncivilised. If anyone reads this, follow in my footsteps. Allow the wolf within to come forth. Say that which goes unsaid, seek vengeance when justice is undone, conquer those who claim to be unconquerable. And if you should fall in your pursuit for balance, you will know that it was for a glorious purpose. Do not let your flame diminish in the darkening of the light, waiting for it to eventually go out.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Fall</Title>
		<Character>Villain</Character>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>Atop the highest pinnacle of an ancient peak a king sat upon his throne. He made sure he was above all others, able to survey his kingdom to the fullest. Many worked for him, farmers, artisans, and other unsavoury crafts. Every year he would throw a feast to demonstrate his mercy. From among the revellers one lucky soul would be chosen to travel out from the confines of his earthly kingdom to the great green places beyond. They praised him for it, working themselves to the brink of exhaustion for the chance to be noticed.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Fall</Title>
		<Character>Villain</Character>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>One day a mother and her child came before the warlord. The feast had not yet come, but still she begged him to take them to the green lands. Her daughter was sick, so she said, and they had no medicine to cure her. At first he refused, but when she threw herself at his feet he knew he could not ignore them. So he agreed to take them to the promised land beyond the valleys. He did not tarry, and soon enough they were making their way down the slopes of the black mountains. He gave them food and water, enough to fill their aching bellies. The mother grew stronger every day but the child only fell deeper into sickness. After several days of travelling she collapsed. She could not be woken from her fever. So they abandoned some of their supplies, and made a makeshift bed for her in the caravan. They were both silent now- the mother constantly attending to the girl, and the king staring grimly ahead at the horizon, deep in thought.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Fall</Title>
		<Character>Villain</Character>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>Beyond the ring of mountains was a desert, a hellish landscape of dusty hills and dry thistle. They had not spoken in days, and the girl's condition had not improved. Suddenly he stopped the caravan, the mules stomping impatiently in the dirt. For a moment he stood in silence, his face turned away from them. Then he faced her, and he said "I cannot lie to you any more, I cannot give you what you seek. There is no green place. But I can give you the caravan, the mules, and whatever is left of our supplies. You can keep travelling if you wish. But you can never return. You cannot tell the others what you have seen. You will destroy them- all of us." So she took it without looking at him, rage burning inside her, and strode into the wilderness.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Fall</Title>
		<Character>Villain</Character>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>She could see him in the distance for some time. He was watching them leave. She had left some water, enough for him to return, but no more. Her emotions roiled inside. She trembled at the thought of what he had done, but she knew why he had done it. They needed to believe there was more to their lives, that maybe one day they could leave for a better place. Only now she knew there was nothing beyond the mountains. Only the heat, the brush, and the broken earth. At one point she passed a massive arch, hewn from an unknown stone, soaring far into the burning sky. It was an evil thing; a monument of death in a dead land. So she passed swiftly by and never again looked back.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Fall</Title>
		<Character>Villain</Character>
		<PartNumber>5</PartNumber>
		<Text>They came upon a small settlement, an oasis of humankind in the desert. They were taken in with open arms, fed, and watered. The group even had a little medicine, and immediately set about tending the child's fever. The girl improved slowly but surely, until one day she could open his eyes. As soon as the others saw he was fit to walk their charity disappeared. They bound the mother, gagged her, and tied her to a wagon. Slavers. She cried out to her child, screaming for her to run. They struck her until she was silent, but it was too late. When they came for the girl they found she had fled into the desert, towards the great mountain wall on the horizon. They sent trackers after her, but they returned with nothing. None would return to that terrible place. She would never know what happened to her child, but she could hope in the face of all she knew that the child would find a better future than she.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A Question of Faith</Title>
		<Character>Survivor</Character>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>Oft I walked the roads of old, now decrepit and hidden by the sands of time. Upon my journeys I came across a band of wandering holy men. As they seemed to be walking the same way as me, I decided I would travel with them. "Hail" I shouted as I approached them. They turned with not the slightest bit of surprise on their faces. "Hail to you to, daughter of the desert" they said in reply. "Will you walk the holy roads with us?" they asked. "Whilst I am no pilgrim I find myself walking the same path, so yes, I will join you in part." I replied. "I see, well, while our destinations may differ, it is the journey that matters most, is it not?" they replied. And so I joined them, introducing myself to them and they to me, all whilst I pondered the meaning of his words.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A Question of Faith</Title>
		<Character>Survivor</Character>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>"Are you a woman of faith?" the leader of the group asked me. "No." I replied. When he saw that I was not going to speak further he asked "And why, may I ask, do you live without the gods in your life?". And so I said "Father, with utmost respect, the gods have left us to rot in the wreckage of the old world. Why should I have faith in them when they have shown that they have no care in us?". He furrowed his brow, then relaxed his face. He smiled and said "Love is unconditional, my daughter, it is not for us to question their ways, nor for us to doubt their love for us. We give our love to them without expecting reciprocity." he said. "That would be a selfish, undeserving love."</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A Question of Faith</Title>
		<Character>Survivor</Character>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>When the evening came and the suns began to set we made camp. Though I would rather have continued on into the night my new companions were not so confident, and I did not want to walk alone. So I sat and watched the light fade as the others busied themselves pitching tents and assembling their fires. Another pilgrim sat next to me. For a while we were silent, but then I asked them "You believe they made it all for us don't you? The sun, the stars, and the earth, all created so that we may live in comfort." "I do" he replied, "but I know you do not. I know what you will say: If the gods can create so much with so little effort then why should we be thankful for something that costs them nothing to give." "How did you know?" I asked. "Because I too felt that way, a long time ago. But someone told me 'It is not the cost of the gift, but the intent that matters.'" he said. "If the gods truly did not care for us, they would have not have given us anything at all."</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A Question of Faith</Title>
		<Character>Survivor</Character>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>When I awoke the next day there was no sign of the pilgrims. I searched in disbelief for any clue or trail that could tell me where they had gone. From the dim light of predawn to the oppressive glare of the midday sun I searched, and still I could find nothing- not a charred log from the fire, nor a lost peg from their canvas tents, not even a single footprint in the dirt. They had simply vanished. When I finally gave up and resolved to continue my journey on, I found the road ahead cleared of sand, and lying before me, a backpack. I opened the pack, and found it filled with food- jars of preserves, bread, and fruit. Bandages it had too, and other necessities, and nestled deep within the pack was a small leather bound book. Its dry pages were crisp to the touch, and inside its front page was a message that read "A gift, given out of love, expecting none in return."</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Silent Gods</Title>
		<Character>Hunter</Character>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>Deep in the salt sea there is a church. It sits above the great saline cracks, under the unbearable heat of the sun. They say it once sat on an island in the midst of a shallow sea, brilliant blue, and teeming with life. It was not this way when I saw it. My father took me there on my tenth birthday. The salty air inside was as stifling as it was hot. I remember feeling the beads of sweat trickle down my back as I sat and listened to the ancient wooden walls creak in the breeze. He stood by the altar at the head of the church, and he commanded me "Son, tell me what you see".</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Silent Gods</Title>
		<Character>Hunter</Character>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>Confused, I looked around the church. There was nothing of note to be seen, other than the ancient building itself. So I told him just that. "And that is exactly why I brought you here." he said. "This is the last church of the old gods, but do you see anyone here? There are no worshippers, no candles, not even a place where to sit." he went on. "This is because the gods do not care for us, boy. They have abandoned us. There will be no response to our prayers. You must learn to make your own path in this world.".</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Silent Gods</Title>
		<Character>Hunter</Character>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>Years later, with the great salt sea and the dessicated church far behind me, I thought back on my father's message. We had travelled so far for him to make that point to me. And yet it has always stuck with me. There are many who still pray for better times- for their children, and their crops, and their sick. But I never have, not since that day. It was not long after that my father took ill. It was the essence that finally took him, confined him to his bed and dishonoured his pride. Not once did he pray as he suffered. He did not ask for the medicine we did not have. He knew his time had come and he consigned himself to his fate.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Silent Gods</Title>
		<Character>Hunter</Character>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>Now I scour the barren wastes of our world doing what the gods will not. The only measure of justice to be found lies in my hands, in the keenness of my eye, and the surety of my arm. Only a fool puts faith in divine justice. And whilst the fool waits, the thief takes what he wishes. The preachers may say what goes around comes around. Karma, destiny, fate, call it what you will. I believe in vengeance. I believe in delivering justice to the unpunished. Mine is the path of retribution, and I do not need the gods to walk it.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
</Characters>