<Necromancer>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Desert</Title>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>You wept. Alone, and in darkness. I watched you across the great cold distance and in you I saw myself. I have brought you here, to my world, so that we might both be saved. We both can look upon these desolate plains with unfamiliar gaze. But this was once my home. Long before the darkness fell these lands were green. I would walk amongst the trees and feel the grass beneath my feet. Now the groves are dead, and I pass like a shadow among them. Only the sun-scorched dirt remains.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Desert</Title>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>There were once five gods who roamed the world. Around them five great kingdoms were founded. Our civilisations grew with time. Miracles became rote; our cities rose high into the heavens and our machines worked the earth. The gods saw they were no longer needed, and so they retreated from the world of man. One day, when we had all but forgotten our roots, they vanished. But the vacuum left by their absence was clear. Something changed, in the air, the earth, and the sea. The essence that binds the world turned on us. It soured the earth and awoke ceaseless winds. The gods are gone, and with them, our humanity.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Desert</Title>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>Ahead lies a dead world- a stagnant place where only barbarism and hopelessness remain. But I believe if we can bring back the gods we can restore it all. I know where they are. They sleep in the place between places, the dark realm beyond the veil of reality. There are five gates that lead to this realm, but they lie dormant, activated by temples long since fallen to the essence. I cannot cleanse the temples, but I can guide you to them. Only together can the gods turn the tide of decay, and offer you the peace which you so dearly seek.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Desert</Title>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>Your path is not an easy one, there will be dangers, both physical and psychological. The essence will seek to claim you. It will burrow into your thoughts and lay seeds of doubt. It once gave strength to the gods, now unbound it breeds only chaos. It feeds on our wants and fear. All you will encounter have succumbed to its influence. Some may still resist. Others, however, will stop at nothing to rid you from the world.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Desert</Title>
		<PartNumber>5</PartNumber>
		<Text>You were lost, but I found you. Your memories have been hidden, for now, at least, but I cannot hide your pain. That you will have to bear. When you are ready I will tell you more. Until then you must endure. Trust in my words, I do not wish to deceive you. The gods can heal your grief, just as they can heal my world.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Desert</Title>
		<PartNumber>6</PartNumber>
		<Text>I have brought you to the kingdom of Eo. Only one temple binds the gateway, and it lies hidden amongst the shifting desert sands. When it is broken return here and place your hands upon the stones. Be prepared, for I do not know what awaits you within. I will be waiting for you on the other side, no matter what happens.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Mountains</Title>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>So it is done, you have passed through the gate and the realm between the shadows. You have done wonderfully. Already I hear Eo's voice on the wind - calling for her lost siblings. How must it feel, to awaken from one nightmare into another, to see your beautiful world in ruins. I was there whilst it happened - I watched the life of the earth fade away. But I was cursed to remain as everything I loved turned to dust. I saw my friends and my family die, as I was doomed to solitude by immortality. I do not feel pity for the dead, wanderer, for it is the living alone who are left who grieve.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Mountains</Title>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>We stand now in the kingdom of Hythinea, the warrior goddess, queen of motherhood. This was once the the backbone of the world. Atop the highest mountains her fortresses were built, and in deepest dells her cities. Gone are the grassy slopes with their grazing flock. Gone are the roads where merchants once ran their goods. Gone are the flowered pastures and gentle rivers. Now there is only dirt and rock amongst the shattered peaks. Dark shadows cast by black crags, and the eyes of evil looking out from dismal caves.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Mountains</Title>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>This was my home before I became The Necromancer. When I was a child the sun rose high above the horizon and the sky was still blue. I was there when the gates were built. I watched as the sands encroach upon our kingdoms, and with them our ties to our brothers and sisters disappear on the desert winds. I remember when the last flowers faded. I remember when the rivers dried up. I remember the day when the brave lost their voice, and the braying of animals was replaced by screams of the dying. I have kept my faith all these years, believing that I would find someone like you to save us. Long have I waited here, Wanderer, but I knew that you would come.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Mountains</Title>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>Again and again I see your fate repeated in my dreams. I watch as the final temple is cleansed, and the last gate illuminated with life. Time and time again I see the gods reverse the wheel of time and raise our cities up from the dust. It has been prophesied, and so it will be. Go now, into the mountains where the cold winds blow and the sun dare not dwell. Find the one who sleeps and return her to us.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Sea</Title>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>I can sense the question in your heart- who is the woman who you dream of? Yes, I have seen your dreams, and I know the dread that grows in your heart. She is your wife, Wanderer, and she is dying. I did not want to tell you before, for I thought that the knowledge would be too much for you to bear. I see now I was wrong, you are stronger than I ever could have thought. There is still time to save her, but you must be fast.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Sea</Title>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>We have come to the most desolate of all places- the sea of salt. There was once a great ocean here, one that spanned between the shores of the land, unbroken for thousands of miles. Now the water is gone, locked up in the frozen poles leaving only salt behind. Only the bones of dead leviathans can tell us what was here. Their harrowing echoes boom in the saline crevasses that criss cross the ancient seabed.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Sea</Title>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>When I was young, my father would talk of the ocean. We lived in the mountains, but his heart was with the sea. He would draw ships when his mind wandered, and we during the summer months we would often find him staring out towards the horizon, his soul somewhere far away. But life kept him from the sea. My mother worked in the city, I had my school, there we a myriad of reasons we could not go. Eventually the procession of time wore away at him, we all grew older, and as the winter of old age set in, the dream of the sea slipped away. My father was not an unhappy man, quite the opposite in fact, but there was always a part of him that was not with us, a part that belonged to the shore, and to the waters of the sea. He is gone now. They all are. Even the sea.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Sea</Title>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>My family remains with me, watching down from the halls of heaven. They are among good people- my friends, other mystics I knew, and thousands of others. They watch me as I hold my vigil on earth, watching, wandering, writing, preserving their memory for those who will come later. My mother and father were not there when the sun tore itself into three, or when the foundations of our cities turned to dust and were borne away by the empty wind. When I die they will know, I will tell them everything I have seen, I will tell them of you, of what we have done. I know they will be proud. That is how my beliefs have remained strong, Wanderer. Not through madness or obsession, but because of my parents love. I do all I do so that those who have lost may love again.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ruins</Title>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>The seasons blend together, winter and summer differentiated only by the height of the sun. The weather does not relent, nor the interminable march of time and the waste it brings. When my vigil began the wounds of war were still fresh in the earth. Slowly they healed, with every spring that passed more flowers would grow, and nature would claim what man had left behind. Soon enough there were no traces to be seen amongst the trees and wild things. Then the essence's influence set in. The flowers would not bloom, the grass wilted and died, and the soil turned to sand. Then the war machines were revealed again, like primordial beasts risen to walk upon the earth once more. Their rusty carcasses standing testament to the permanence of mankind's work. There they rest still, waiting for the end.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ruins</Title>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>It is always darkest before the dawn, or so they say. There can be no triumph without sacrifice. Even as the sickness that pervades this world tightens its grip, there is still a chance for redemption. My people have known for a long time that our sacrifice must be paid in blood. There were many of us in the beginning. So many who gave their lives to halt the spread of evil. Scholars, teachers, students, clerics- all those who could dedicate their minds to our cause, these were my people. They called us the Mystics, a name we came to embrace as time went on. It was they who made me what I am today, incapable of death, but unable to exist with the living.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ruins</Title>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>In the first days I did nothing but roam the earth, documenting what I saw. But the deserts spread faster than I could, the animals retreated and died, and a great pall was set upon the earth. Still I searched for pockets of life- a mountain tarn still teeming with fish, or a woodland hidden away in some far corner. Never did I find anything, and I came to realise I never would. 'But my hope has never waned.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ruins</Title>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>We are nearing the end. I feel the air changing as you advance. It is lighter, as if a weight were lifting. Even the sun seems brighter to my eyes. Soon I will be able to show you the wonders of this world. When the gods return we will walk the ground together. I will give you the life you desire, and you will take my hand as we watch an ancient dawn become new once more. We are so close to the end, Wanderer. The next gate will take you to the ruins of our greatest city, where the lingering ghosts of the dead cry out for life.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Wasteland</Title>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>The winds are changing, old currents blow once more, interrupting the monotonous cycle that has gone on for too long. The gods are waking, their spirits waking the world from its terminal sleep. The essence grows agitated, pulling at invisible threads in the air. It resists their control, for now, but when Corypthos awakens it will relent- bound once more. The deserts will retreat, pushed back by the tide of life that yearns to spill across the barren earth.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Wasteland</Title>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>Our struggle is almost at an end, Wanderer. I see the trauma in your eyes grow with every moment that passes. You are remembering what it was you left behind, that I rescued you from. Yes, what you fear to be real is indeed so. Corpythos, lord of life, awaits you in the Wasteland. He can bring her back, Wanderer. So too can he free me, return me my body so that I may walk among the trees once again. And my people, he will return them too, oh how soon it will be. Oh, I am sorry, I cannot hide my elation. I know you suffer, but you cannot know how I have suffered, and how soon that suffering will come to an end. When it is done, when duty fulfilled and my vigil over, I will return home, and I will sit as my father sat, and I will watch the sun set as it did so many years ago.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>End</Title>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>It happens slowly at first. The suns swell and grow bright. The air turns still and the noises of the earth and of battle fade away. Light envelops me, signaled by a peal of thunder so loud as to shake the foundations of heaven. I hold my breath in the bright void and shut my eyes against the glare. In the distance I can hear the Necromancer's cries. She is weeping, screaming, in sadness and in pain, but that too diminishes until I am left in utter silence.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>End</Title>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>It was never to be. The Necromancer's world could never be saved. The fifth tomb is empty, abandoned years ago. The gods are no more, and now the long awaited doom of her world has finally come. I feel my fate coalescing as the memories return. They are painful, breaching the surface of consciousness all at once. Among them is her face, eyes closed and silent.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>End</Title>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>Then I am in another world. My own world. I look up at a brilliant blue sky illuminated by the light of a single white star. Another change, and I am in a starkly white room. The only door into the room is shut, the walls reflect on the marble floor below. And then I see her, lying in a raised bed, wrapped in ivory sheets.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>End</Title>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>I take her hand, hesitantly at first. As our hands touch the physical memory of her returns, and I take her up in my arms. She tells me she is sorry that she has to go. She chokes on the words as she tells me she does not want to leave me alone. I tell her there is nothing to forgive. I say I am sorry I cannot go with her, but that I would carry her forever with me.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>End</Title>
		<PartNumber>5</PartNumber>
		<Text>We brush away our tears and turn our talk to old times- our children and the places we have been. As the day turns to night she becomes ever quieter, so I draw her close and take up the conversation. Later, as the light of the sun breaks the horizon, her soft laughter at my stories grows silent. I knew then that she was gone, and that I was alone.|br||br|I still see her in my mind- as young and beautiful as she was on the day we first met.|br||br|But the memories will fade with me, and all will be borne away on the wind.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
</Necromancer>