<Wanderer>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A New World</Title>
		<Environment>Desert</Environment>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>The land before me is just as the Necromancer said- dark and dying. Even the dry ground seems to creak with hunger, eager to slake its thirst with my blood. There are others here. They are vague shapes on the horizon and subtle whispers on the wind. Purgatorial souls - fearful and wary. If I am to be alone in my journey then that is the way it must be.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A New World</Title>
		<Environment>Desert</Environment>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>Sensations come and go, like memories without context. Warm light on my back. The green glow of a sunlit canopy, and dappled colour on the ground where the light breaks through. They match nothing of what I have experienced. Here there are no living trees, no leaf-laden boughs, only dead roots, withered stumps, and the stifling heat.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A New World</Title>
		<Environment>Desert</Environment>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>What was once familiar is now foreign to me - the sky a deep shade of crimson, lit by the weak glow of three ailing suns, and the air heavy with dread expectation. At night the heavens glitter with the light of unknown constellations. I am not sure if I will ever share the Necromancer's faith, but if the alternative is a life of solitude and fear then I will go wherever she bids.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A New World</Title>
		<Environment>Desert</Environment>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>Though the ground is arid and the air still, the desert is not completely devoid of life. The gentle rustle of the breeze is broken by the coo of small birds and the churr of insects. The plants I have seen are as brittle and cracked as the dry sand they grow in. The few fruit they bear are wizened, and coloured with such evil hues I would not dare to touch them.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A New World</Title>
		<Environment>Desert</Environment>
		<PartNumber>5</PartNumber>
		<Text>More unsettling than the blood red sky is the loss I feel inside. I cannot shake it. What has the Necromancer hidden from me? I cannot remember anything of where I came, nor how I came to be here. It is as if there is a fog in my mind, pushing all else beyond the boundaries of my subconscious.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A New World</Title>
		<Environment>Desert</Environment>
		<PartNumber>6</PartNumber>
		<Text>I have slept well here. I have even dreamed- for the first time in a long time. In my dreams I am in a cavernous room. There are no walls. Far above I can see a stone roof, arching away into the blackness beyond. I let myself lie back and drift in silence on the murky currents of my thoughts.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A New World</Title>
		<Environment>Desert</Environment>
		<PartNumber>7</PartNumber>
		<Text>I feel my emotions ebb and flow like the tide, and I allow myself to be borne away on their currents. With every swell come glimpses of my past, clearer now. But as every swell passes, so do these memories fade. I cannot hold onto them in this bleak and desolate world.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A New World</Title>
		<Environment>Desert</Environment>
		<PartNumber>8</PartNumber>
		<Text>It was neither chance nor fate that brought me here. The Necromancer was adamant that I was chosen for this task, that I alone am able to find and awaken the gods, but can I believe her? It seems likely that I am just one of many. Doomed to wander, endlessly searching for purpose until the end of my days.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A New World</Title>
		<Environment>Desert</Environment>
		<PartNumber>9</PartNumber>
		<Text>My dreams are strange. When I am in them they seem so utterly convincing that I wake with a start. The shift to reality is unwelcome, for in my dreams I am at peace, and in this nightmare world I cannot escape the weight of my grief.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>A New World</Title>
		<Environment>Desert</Environment>
		<PartNumber>10</PartNumber>
		<Text>I am not a man of faith. I do not believe in gods or demons. But I will do what I can to heal the wound inside me. I cannot live with it, and I fear it will only deepen with time. I have already seen so much that does not make sense, so I will find the gates, and perhaps I will find deliverance.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>Four gates remain, and I am all but spent. To follow the path to open the Gate of Eo has been burdensome enough, but with four more in wait I am not sure if I am able to go on. I feel only dread at the thought journey before me. There is no doubt that greater dangers lie in the wilderness ahead. I just hope that I will be prepared.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>The gently rolling dunes are gone. Scree clad mountains rise up in their stead. From abyssal floor to mist shrouded peaks they tower. The ground is steep, sharp, and treacherous underfoot. Darkness abounds - the light of the sun veiled by the long shadows of the mountains. Beneath me the earth groans and strains, trembling at the forces at work deep below.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>Before coming here I would awaken violently, panting and covered in layer of sweat, white knuckled fists digging bloody nails into my palms. I know this, for I can see the scars in my hands, even if I cannot recall the memories. Instead I wander the hallways of my dreams. The cavernous hall in which I walk broken by monolithic pillar, whose trunks rise unbroken to the ceiling above.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>When last I dreamed I saw a distant figure. I called out, but there was no reply. When I approached, it faded into the darkness, only to reappear further away. At first it vexed me, so I approached slowly, only to find it vanish again. Once more I tried, more carefully still, and this time the figure did not vanish. When at last I came upon it, I found a woman. She was clad in ivory robes, and asleep upon the floor. Suddenly I was overcome with unease, for when I looked upon her face, I realised I knew her.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>5</PartNumber>
		<Text>A shadow lives within me, lurking in the back of my mind. Inside its inky depths is something from my past that I do not want to remember. It swells to fill every crevice of mind, and I cannot think of anything else. Just as I try to bring the memory into focus it shrinks and retreats into my subconscious.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>6</PartNumber>
		<Text>Hythinea's kingdom is one of balance. At once terrifying and peaceful. Even the simplest journeys require absolute focus to avoid cutting my hands or twisting my ankle. But moments of peace come too - times when I can just sit upon the rocks and be alone. The wind drowns out the ill thoughts, and my mind is lifted of its burdens.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>7</PartNumber>
		<Text>The shadow in me darkens, roiling like a storm eager to break. I worry that it will consume me. If it does not then this world surely will. Every breath I take languishes deep in my lungs, and the relief that water and food brings is too swiftly replaced with thirst and hunger.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>8</PartNumber>
		<Text>Again I saw the woman in my dreams. This time she came to meet me, her long hair flowing with her robes as she walked. She sat upon her knees, and I saw the floor around us was no longer dark stone, but white marble, and the blackness around us lifted, revealing an infinite expanse of marbled pillars. There we sat together, waiting for something. But something never came, and I woke confused, with only a greater sense of loss than before.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>9</PartNumber>
		<Text>Flashes of memory come and go, stirring up hope and despair within me. I see unfamiliar faces, solemn, with heads bowed. Like a great beast I feel my past approaching. It is distant now, but draws closer, growing ever more defined, until the full horror of its figure is clear.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>10</PartNumber>
		<Text>The beating heart of the earth resounds through the landscape. And with each beat I count down my life, one moment at a time. The shadowy claws of defeat desperately pull at the sanity I struggle to maintain. The direness of my quest becomes more apparent every day, for it is one that may claim my very soul.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>11</PartNumber>
		<Text>I call her my angel. She will not tell me her true name. Though I recognise her face, it is her eyes that are most familiar to me. They are wide, with green irises, but burdened by the dark rings of sleepless nights. I have spoken to her, well, whispered really, for I am afraid to upset the fragility of the dream. I know she spoke to, but now I cannot recall what it was she said.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>12</PartNumber>
		<Text>Whilst my vision grows dull, my dreams become more vivid, and with them she becomes more alive. I resent her absence when I wake, I think only of her as I walk through twilight lands, and the desire in my heart grows as weariness sets in. I am unaffected by the sting of injury, or the pang of hunger. I survive only to see the day through, so that I might be with her at its end.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>13</PartNumber>
		<Text>Day and night, hour after hour, ceaseless in their howling do the mountain winds blow. From the throaty gusts across the wide mountain passes, to the shrill cry through narrow crevasses. The call of the mountain lords echo between every stone and every wall. I cannot see but one flower growing upon the mountainside, only poisonous vines and rusted metal. How cruel time is to bring beauty to ruin whilst leaving evil untouched.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>14</PartNumber>
		<Text>Now we speak more freely, and her words remain in my memory even after I wake. I must know who she is, whether she is a part of my psyche, or just another apparition in this wasted world. I ask her how she knows where we are, how she knows who I am. I ask gently at first, but my curiosity turns to frustration when she will not answer, and as it so easily does, my frustration turns to anger.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Ebb and Flow</Title>
		<Environment>Mountains</Environment>
		<PartNumber>15</PartNumber>
		<Text>She turns her face to hide, but I can see the tears upon her cheek. I realise now that it does not matter who she is. She has not come to me to be my guide. She is not here to lead me to my fabled destiny. She is here to be with me, to give me respite when I sleep and to give me something to live for when my body is spent.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>A new land, different to the last in every way, but the heavy sense of dread in my stomach remains. An endless plain of salty islands - a landscape shattered by the endless beat of the sun. Only in the crevasses between the islands is it cool enough to survive. Some are small, almost hairline fractures, whilst others are so wide that the light of my torch does not reach the other side.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>There is a curse laid upon this land. It is a curse that threatens to bring me to my knees. It weighs heavy upon my shoulders, begs me to give in to darkness. I utter a prayer under my breath to ward off the voices, but the Necromancer was right, there are no gods listening here.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>The gate is the only constant on my journey. It stands some twenty metres high, constructed of smooth rock with no visible evidence of tool marks. It is as if there is only one gate, existing simultaneously across the five realms, like a nail hammered into layers of wood, binding the world together at a single point.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>Sometimes I hear distant voices, muffled as if speaking from another room. It is as if the walls of the world are thinning, bringing the living and the dead close to each other. Some voices are louder than others, but they go quiet as soon as I speak out to them, leaving me in silence once again.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>5</PartNumber>
		<Text>I came across the hull of an ancient boat. Though its mast was broken, and its sail long since carried away by the winds, I could see that it once would have flown across the waves swiftly. The planks of its hull were rotten, and its metal supports warped and rusted, but I could tell that it was once strong and sleek, able to glide atop the water's surface and weather the heaviest of waves. Even now, shattered, and strewn across the wastes, the beauty of the vessel was clear to me, and I will carry that beauty until the end of my days.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>6</PartNumber>
		<Text>The daytime sun bears down on me, burning my exposed skin. Even the salt seems to sizzle beneath its rays. So I am forced to walk in the shadows - my eyes accustomed now to the twilight gloom. The maze of salt hides the remains of the ancient sea - the bones of ancient creatures half buried in the walls, and the bleached wrecks of ships strewn across the seabed.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>7</PartNumber>
		<Text>When the Necromancer first told me of dead gods and ancient prophecies I thought her mad. Now I am not sure what I believe. Perhaps my hysteria has grown to such heights that I cannot distinguish dream from reality. Or perhaps it is all as it seems. Without evidence either way, I can only have faith in her words.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>8</PartNumber>
		<Text>I told the angel what the Necromancer told me, and she nodded with a faint smile across her lips. After that we spoke more freely. To me she is still a stranger, I know I have memories of her, but they resist my call. She listens to me, and I her. We talk of things we love and things we lost. It does not matter if she is real, for she is real enough to keep me going.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>9</PartNumber>
		<Text>My steps falter, and I come to a stop. My path is unclear. I see only a destination that leads to another - markers in the desert, endless but going nowhere. The shadow grows and my hope dwindles. There, deep inside me, there is my goal. I must dispel the clouds, but I am afraid of what I will find. No, I will wait. For now at least. I cannot face it yet.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>10</PartNumber>
		<Text>Where have the seas gone? Where are the tides that broke on salty shores and flowed around the now bleached corals? Life has vanished, never to return. It leaves a vacuum that cannot be filled. The water has been locked up at the ends of the earth - a memory of the world that was. The oceans are forgotten, the fisherfolk fled, but what remains must go on.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>11</PartNumber>
		<Text>Once again my feet disobey me. I am stuck, as if chained to the spot, but it is only my mind that holds me. "Go on", I tell myself but will not listen. "One more step" I say out loud, to no avail. For I know it to be a lie, there are many steps ahead, and for what? To what end am I journeying? The struggle is within me, not out there. Why do I desire so strongly to find the gods I do not believe in?</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>12</PartNumber>
		<Text>The realisation dawns. The gods are a comfort. I try hard to believe they care about me, that they can fix me, because I do not want to face my demons alone. It is why the Necromancer still believes. But face them I must, before they destroy me.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>13</PartNumber>
		<Text>Faith is what carries me forward. Not faith in the gods, but faith in myself. It turns my weakness into strength, so that I may see the light that casts the shadow. Though my steps are laboured I can see where my path leads, and so I go on with purpose - to free the gods, The Necromancer, and myself.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>14</PartNumber>
		<Text>My dreams are no longer calming. My angel is more animate than ever, and it is draining me to my core. I wake feeling both physically and mentally exhausted. One moment she laughs and smiles, the marble floor radiating with soothing light as she does. The next she is on the ground, kicking and screaming with pain and rage, locked in her dream-prison.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>15</PartNumber>
		<Text>During one of her fits she became suddenly still, contorted on the ground with fists curled and ragged breath. She turned her eyes to me, and I saw pain deep in them. I can do nothing to sooth her, but I would still rather be with her in the chaos of my dreams, than alone and awake in this midnight world.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>16</PartNumber>
		<Text>She said that something was coming, something terrible, and that I must prepare myself. I tell her I know that she is dying, and I tell her I will come for her. At this she shook her head and wept. The darkness began to close in, and the dream came to an end. When I opened my eyes I did not see an ivory angel, only the dead sky above.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>17</PartNumber>
		<Text>I can see the sickness growing in her. Her hair has become thin, and her face gaunt. Even her robes have turned an ashen shade of grey. Her beautiful eyes are now sullen and set deep in dark sockets. She stumbles often when we walk together, and I fear that her time draws near. I must escape this terrible place. Even if I cannot save her, I must be with her. I will not let her be alone.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>18</PartNumber>
		<Text>I hold her in my lap, and I watch her chest rise and fall. We have nothing to say, so we sit are silent. I hold her close. The dream-light is fading, drawing closer around us like a cocoon of darkness. I promise her we are close now, there is not long left. I am not sure if she can hear, but it does not matter, it was said as much for me as it was for her.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>19</PartNumber>
		<Text>She tried to speak to me last night, but I could not hear her, for she was too far away. I tried to run to her, but I could not get close enough for her to hear. Instead I could see her eyes wide with terror, and her mouth open to scream. Now I could hear her, but it was a muffled scream as if from under water.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>Twilight of the Gods</Title>
		<Environment>Sea</Environment>
		<PartNumber>20</PartNumber>
		<Text>She screamed and screamed, the muscles on her atrophied arms tensed and relaxed in spasm. Then I too was screaming on my knees with my head in my heads. It did not end, it just went on, the endless wailing, and the tears. All I wanted to do was to hold her again, to stop her screams. But I could not.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>A terrible sight is before me: a great city in ruins. Buildings that once reached far into the heavens above now reduced to skeletons of twisted metal, their foundations shattered and exposed. There is no life here- no birdsong on the breeze, only the hollow wail of the wind.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>A red glow punches through the darkness. Her eyes stare unblinking at its source, though I cannot make it out in the gloom. "Go" she says. So I do, cradling her light frame in my arms. As we approach I see a fountain made of black stone, and in it a pool of glowing red liquid. "Drink" she says, touching her lips gently. I hesitate before lowering her to the pool to drink. The moment the liquid touches her lips she falls limp. Her body slips from my hands to the marble floor. She takes two haggard breaths interspersed with bloody coughs. Then she grows still and will not wake.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>She lies unmoving on the floor. I try all I can to bring her back to life. Just as I feel hope slipping away she jerks awake, eyes wide, spitting red and black liquid upon herself. Before I have a chance to say anything, she points to the fountain, and to her lips, and again she says "Drink". I shake my head, feeling the tears rolling down my cheeks. Again she points to her lips. I hang my head in despair, but I know it is what she needs.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>She is silent now, her eyes will not open, she does not move. I would think her dead if it were not for the shallow breathing of her chest. The fervour of past dreams is gone, replaced instead by anxious waiting. I stand in the endless marble room, unable to do anything but watch her rest.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>5</PartNumber>
		<Text>Time passes imperceptibly slowly, and I cannot take my eyes from her. Truly this is hell, to watch and not know what to do but wait. Wait until the hours of my life are spent. I wake slowly now, gazing at the sky and unable to rise. My body betrays me. Muscles tug feebly at aching tendons. I fear I am losing myself to this world, and to her.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>6</PartNumber>
		<Text>Waiting, watching, pacing to and fro. Every night stuck in my dream prison. Forced to watch her pale skin shiver. I can only watch when the spasms strike- the pain contorting her grey face. Yet still she sleeps. I talk to her when I can, but often I cannot find words worth saying. Instead I brush her pale hair and hold her cold hands in my lap. And despite everything I know, everything I have done, and everything I have seen, I pray for it to be over.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>7</PartNumber>
		<Text>Why do I feel as though this has happened before, in another world. The painful wait for remission, and the fear of relapse. Is my mind playing tricks on me, or is this a part of the despair that has been hidden from me? Could it be a warning I wonder- to make haste to finish my quest. Or is just a fever dream brought on by the gradual onset of the essence's affliction.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>8</PartNumber>
		<Text>I will never forget the pain on her face as she drank, or the pain I felt as I held her, thinking she would never wake. But wake she did, rousing slowly from her death sleep. She looked well once again, her skin warm and the mania driven from her eyes. She lifted her hand to mine, and kissed my cheek. I carried her away from the vile fountain, and as I did the light began to return.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>9</PartNumber>
		<Text>Finally things seem to have changed for the better. A warm glow replaces ghostly pallor and her eyes bright once again. I rejoice, and tell her I believed she was lost. "I'm sorry" she says. But I tell her not to be sorry, that she cannot hold herself to blame. I tell her of the things I had remembered since we last spoke- happy memories, places I had been. She nods and listens, though her thoughts seem far away.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>10</PartNumber>
		<Text>The city is ancient. How ancient I wonder? How long since the guards abandoned their posts. Was it the fire-laced breath of artillery that brought down the city's walls or merely the inescapable erosion of time? Through it all The Necromancer has haunted the world, or so she says. She watched the essence dig take ahold of her world, and not once has she seen its grip weaken.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>11</PartNumber>
		<Text>Fierce have been the ravages of time upon this ancient city. Even now there remain signs of plight- dark craters, munition cases- tarnished and spent. Even the rusted carcasses of war machines litter the land. But there are no bones, no bodies, no graves, no markers of human inhabitation to speak of.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>12</PartNumber>
		<Text>At first I thought I was dreaming, but no, there she is, standing before me. A vision, but still with me here in the waking world. She looks better, her features full and no longer sunken, and her smile has returned. She is not near enough to hear me call out, so I wave to her instead. For a moment it seems as though she cannot see me, but she waves back. Then as suddenly as it began, the vision ends.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>13</PartNumber>
		<Text>The old world has been swept away. It is good the Necromancer cannot be with me to see it. If she were to lay her eyes upon the ruins she surely would fall to her knees and weep. Perhaps that is why she whispers to me from the darkness - to shield herself from reality, to allow herself to have hope in a place where none can be found.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>14</PartNumber>
		<Text>I cannot imagine the things The Necromancer has had to endure. Sometimes I think my burden insignificant compared to hers. After all what is the worth of one life against that of an entire civilisation? But we all have our own cross to bear. The more I stay here, the more I see what has been lost. When this is all over I will return to help her, if I can.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>15</PartNumber>
		<Text>The shadow within grows, pressing against my skull. I feel despair well up uncontrollably. My breathing comes shallow and my heart rises into my throat. Panic. My vision tunnels and I collapse to the floor. Then before me I see her, my angel, her cool hand upon my forehead. Memories explode within me, I see her pale face, flowers, white sheets, blood. "Breathe" she says. I close my eyes and breath deep- once, twice, feeling the despair dissipate. Then I open them only to find her gone.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>16</PartNumber>
		<Text>I do not think I could bear to watch as the places I know fall into disrepair and the people I love age and die. I could not bear to be alone to be without someone to ease my pain. Left with only my unquietable thoughts for company, reliving my lost past over and over. I would watch my past self and wish that I could change the things that can never be changed. And I would wish to go back and spend one last moment with those who are gone.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>17</PartNumber>
		<Text>Another vision. I can see her in the corner of my eye. She sits at the top of a tall set of steps. As I reach the top I realise she is not looking at me, but at the base of a broken statue. Atop the statues' weathered head is a crown- tarnished but still golden. This man, a king, was once well loved by his people. So loved that even today it remained untouched by scavengers. She points at the inscription at its base but I cannot make out the words. The raised stone letters have been worn away by the wind. I will never know his name.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>18</PartNumber>
		<Text>I remember a story I heard once, about an old man. He lived alone in an old cottage. Like him the building had not aged well, its walls were cracked and the roof fallen in. He was bitter, and set in his ways, and went out only to buy from the local village what he could not make himself. He had not always been bitter, he had not always been alone. One day there were children playing outside his window. He ignored them as best he could, but an errant ball missed its mark and came through his window with a crash. So he yelled at the children, and drove them back to the village. When he returned he cleared up the pieces of shattered glass, but could not repair the window. He did not want to return to the village, and so he left it- a gaping void in the side of his house.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>19</PartNumber>
		<Text>Time passed, and still the window remained broken. The old man could not repair it himself, and did not have the money to pay to have it mended. So the thought of it drifted from his mind, at least until Autumn came. Strong winds rocked the aged house whilst lashes of rain made their way in through the open window. Day after day it came through until not an inch of the house remained dry. But the old man ignored it- after all, he had endured worse.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>20</PartNumber>
		<Text>Then the cold weather came, bringing snow and frost and ice. The old man huddled for warmth in his broken home, his fire dwindling and his supplies low. Finally he relented, and went to the village to beg to have the window repaired. But it was too late, nobody had the tools to fix the window, as broken and warped as it was. They offered him shelter, but his pride took him back home. So there he slept, in the cold and the light of the dying fires, waiting for Spring to come. But there would be no Spring for him, only a deep sleep and a white light, followed by oblivion.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>21</PartNumber>
		<Text>I saw her once again. She sat outside a ruined building reclining on a small drift of sand. So I sat with her, and I asked her how she had escaped her dream prison, but she only gave me a knowing smile and changed the conversation. I do not belong to this world, yet I am growing comfortable here. I am afraid that if I leave I will lose her.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>22</PartNumber>
		<Text>I dream. I ask her where she will go when I return home, but she only smiles and holds her fingers to her lips. I do not pursue the question. I begin to tell her I do not want to lose her, that she must stay with me, but as the words start to leave my mouth I am struck by a flash of painful memories. I awake with a jolt, confused by the bitter-sweet dream. It will not be long before the journey is over.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>23</PartNumber>
		<Text>I turn my ear to the wind and I listen for the gods. I cry out for them, but the only response I find is in the whisper of the sand. I want to hear them, even for a moment, to know they are there. Maybe The Necromancer with her mystic ways is able to hear what I cannot. The world does not feel any different to me.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The Ruination of Man</Title>
		<Environment>Ruins</Environment>
		<PartNumber>24</PartNumber>
		<Text>I see it in my sleep. I hear it in silent places. I even catch glimpses of it when I speak. The darkness, the despair, the weight that lies inside. It is the cold in the pit in my stomach at night, the bleak thoughts when I am alone. The dread thought waxes- the terrible thought that things will not always be. It is the human fear that gives life brilliance. I realise now I have always felt it, but only now that I face the consequence of the fear do I recognise it.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The End of All Things</Title>
		<Environment>Wasteland</Environment>
		<PartNumber>1</PartNumber>
		<Text>Here I stand, in the Eternal Wasteland, at the end of all things, searching for something I cannot find, running from something I cannot remember. It is fitting that, if I should die, I should die here, in this bleak landscape, devoid of memory, no evidence of the past, and no future to speak of. At least it would be a peaceful death, with no-one to see, and no-one to mourn.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The End of All Things</Title>
		<Environment>Wasteland</Environment>
		<PartNumber>2</PartNumber>
		<Text>Though at least a thousand years have passed the scars of the war remain untouched here. The earth has died, and cannot harbour life. Canyons criss cross the landscape, and within them so do the tracks of ancient war machines. The spirits of the dead linger, striking the ground as bolts of lightning, reminding the living that this world is not theirs.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The End of All Things</Title>
		<Environment>Wasteland</Environment>
		<PartNumber>3</PartNumber>
		<Text>I have seen the gods. I know them to be real. Yet I still cannot believe in them. I simply cannot accept that they can do anything to help me. Indeed they might be able to change this world, and in turn help the Necromancer, but they cannot help me. I will not hide from reality any longer. I have looked for comfort in faith, I have tried to ignore my pain, but the only way to be rid of it is to confront it.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The End of All Things</Title>
		<Environment>Wasteland</Environment>
		<PartNumber>4</PartNumber>
		<Text>I admit to myself, I have been selfish. I am not looking for the tombs because I wish to help the Necromancer or her world. I do it because I want to be free of my own suffering. At least now I can empathise with her, though she may be blinded by her faith. Together though, we can work together, and perhaps we both can summon the courage to face down our demons.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The End of All Things</Title>
		<Environment>Wasteland</Environment>
		<PartNumber>5</PartNumber>
		<Text>The gods are gone, fled from this world. The vaults of their tombs are empty, their souls lost to this world. The ingenuity of man has failed. It is a sad truth, impossible to bear, yet it is the truth. It is a truth born upon a wind that lifts the weight from my shoulders and draws the despair from my lungs. It provides me with a certainty, where before there was only uncertainty. This dark, dim, and despairing world is doomed. There is nothing left to do, but accept our fate.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The End of All Things</Title>
		<Environment>Wasteland</Environment>
		<PartNumber>6</PartNumber>
		<Text>There is nothing that can bring us back from the beyond. The suns will fade and shrink, and the land will freeze beneath the starless skies, and all the beasts upon the earth will huddle together for warmth as they take their final breaths on this world. The Necromancer cannot accept this fact, and therein lies the root of her madness.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The End of All Things</Title>
		<Environment>Wasteland</Environment>
		<PartNumber>7</PartNumber>
		<Text>I pity her, for I know her struggle. I do not know where she will go when the last gate is opened. I do not think she will ever be whole again. Whoever she was all those years ago is not who she is now. In some ways I envy her blind belief, with it I could ignore the revelation that is coming, but I cannot make myself blind, instead I will have to face the truth.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The End of All Things</Title>
		<Environment>Wasteland</Environment>
		<PartNumber>8</PartNumber>
		<Text>I can hear in her voice that her suffering grows. With every passing moment her faith is tested, the doubt grows in her mind. She has seen the destruction of her home, her world, and her people. She forfeited her life because she believed that one day the world would be cleansed of its corruption. That belief grew stronger with time, growing ever less rational, consuming her. But she had to believe it, because only by the saving the world could her life be saved.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The End of All Things</Title>
		<Environment>Wasteland</Environment>
		<PartNumber>9</PartNumber>
		<Text>We all are prey to irrationality, we must hold fast to the belief that our dark days precede the light. Without it we would be paralysed in hopelessness. Only through this belief are we able to change the course of our lives. We can push against the currents of reality rather than allow ourselves to be swept away. To give in is not in our nature, to lay down our arms at the feet of our aggressors rather than fight for what we hold dear. Our belief allows us to overcome horror and sorrow, and go on striving for better days, even when we ourselves may not see them.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The End of All Things</Title>
		<Environment>Wasteland</Environment>
		<PartNumber>10</PartNumber>
		<Text>When the time comes, as it does for all of us, when the dissonance in our mind comes to a crescendo, our lives change irreversibly. Either we succumb to the alluring voice of denial, or we accept the harsh voice of reality.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The End of All Things</Title>
		<Environment>Wasteland</Environment>
		<PartNumber>11</PartNumber>
		<Text>We shared another quiet night. She looked well again, though there was a sadness in her voice that couldn't be displaced. She asked me about the world, but I did not wish to tell her about it. I sensed that her fate is somehow related to the fate of the gods. Instead I told her that the essence was retreating, that it would not be long before I opened the final gate. I expected her to be elated, to beam and throw her arms around me. Instead she smiled weakly, and became quiet. I did not speak further. I did not know what to say, so I let the silence say it for me. We held hands, and when the time came to wake, I kissed her softly. As I left the dream world she held her hand out to me, and said she loved me.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The End of All Things</Title>
		<Environment>Wasteland</Environment>
		<PartNumber>12</PartNumber>
		<Text>Now I am alone. When I fell asleep she was gone. I called out for her, but there was no answer. I ran through the endless corridors of my mind to find her, but there was nothing but emptiness. I knew she would not return. I had not opened the gates in time, and now she was gone forever. I sat in my dream world, overwhelmed with emotion. Despair and relief washed over me in equal measures. She would not be in pain any longer, but I do not think I can go on without her. The world is so bleak, so harsh, that without hope I cannot hope to overcome it. Despite our short time together, I will not be able to forget her, I know she will be with me until my last breath.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
	<StoryPart>
		<Title>The End of All Things</Title>
		<Environment>Wasteland</Environment>
		<PartNumber>13</PartNumber>
		<Text>The fog has cleared, and the memories return. The woman, the angel of my dreams, she was real once, a long time ago. I know this, because I was there with her at the end. She believed we would meet again, beyond the veil, she believed it because she had to believe it. Because it was the only thing that would ease the truth of her passing, we knew that nothing could be done for either of us. I am not sure if I believed that we would meet again, but the lie was so sweet. We used the lie to spend our last times in peace and not fear. To pretend to each other as if we were going on a long journey was far easier than to speak a final farewell.</Text>
	</StoryPart>
</Wanderer>